# Asia Hoe

## PRODUCT DESIGNER







0

GitHub



(646) 504-2742



## **PROFILE**

With 7 years of experience across multiple creative disciplines, I combine agile UX strategies and front-end development, to research, design, prototype, and test simple, meaningful, and memorable experiences for people. I love learning and trying new things. I thrive where work meets play, and curiosity, compassion, and authenticity are central to the design ethos and culture.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Gamechaser

New York, NY

Jan. 2015 - Present

## **Product Designer (Freelance)**

CODE

UX

UI

UX

UX

Redesigning multi-platform game chat app through sketches, mockups in Sketch, user testing, prototyping in Invision, and coding in HTML/CSS in collaboration with a small team of developers using Bitbucket revision control.

## Sawhorse Media

New York, NY

May. 2014 - Aug. 2014

# **UX/UI** Designer (Freelance)

Interviewed agency professionals to inform a redesign of the checkout experience for the Shorty Awards Industry applicants website. Compiled extensive notes and audio to inform sketches and interactive Axure prototype.

# Digitas Health

New York, NY

Feb. 2014 - Apr. 2014

# Senior Interaction Designer (Freelance)

Led card sorting exercises to inform mental models, site maps, wireframes, heuristic analyses, and functional specifications docs in agile, fast-paced, and collaborative agency. Clients include several Pfizer and Bristol-Myers Squibb brands for consumer and healthcare professional facing websites.

#### MeeGenius

**₽** N

New York, NY

Nov. 2013

# **UI** Designer (Freelance)

iOS

UI

Designed and implemented changes for children's iOS ebook application and accompanying responsive website under tight holiday deadlines in a fast-paced, highly cooperative startup environment.

## New York Life Insurance

Sleepy Hollow, NY

🗂 Jan. 2011 - May. 2013

## **UX** Designer

Led user interviews and usability tests with interactive prototypes for several highly-trafficked internal web applications. Developed styleguides to govern best design practices. Maintained documentation and visual assets for parallel projects. Served as Web Consultant and Journalist for multiple cultural and special interest aligned Employee Resource Groups.

## 15 Minutes Media

Brooklyn, NY

🗂 Jun. 2010 - Oct. 2010

# **Design Associate**

Updated client websites with standards compliant HTML/CSS. Developed email newsletters and debugged for discrepancies across most clients and platforms. Authored several posts for company blog, *Everybody's Famous*. Developed and maintained wireframes and other documentation for clients. Planned and directed a project, acting as a liaison between team and client.

# Bryn Mawr College

Sleepy Hollow, NY

🛱 Sep.. 2006 - May. 2010

# Web Developer & Office Assistant

Updated and maintained the Civic Engagement Office website and its subsidiaries using HTML, CSS, PHP, and WordPress. Developed promotional materials for events, including fliers, pamphlets, email newsletters, and *Civic Matters* publication to increase awareness and participation in civic engagement opportunities both on and off campus.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Metis

UX & Front-End Development

New York, NY

Sep. 2014 - Dec. 2014

# **General Assembly**

UX Design Immersive

New York, NY

🗂 Jun. 2013 - Aug. 2013

# Bryn Mawr College

r English

Bryn Mawr, PA

📛 Sep. 2005 - May. 2010

## **SKILLS**

User Research & Testing
Competitive Analysis
Heuristic Analysis
Content Strategy
Sketching & Wireframing
Rapid Prototyping
Content Strategy
Social Media
HTML5 & CSS3 (Sass)
JavaScript & jQuery
Agile Development

## **TOOLS**

CODE

UX

IJX

UX

UI

UI

UI

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign Sketch 3 Axure Invision GitHub BitBucket WordPress